<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


     <string name="descripcion1">Jardín, Antioquia, is one of the most beautiful towns in Colombia, a very colorful and welcoming country town that is surrounded by incredible natural landscapes, waterfalls, mountains and great biodiversity.
        The municipality of Jardín is located in the southwest of Antioquia, on the slopes of the mountain range and less than 4 hours from the city of Medellín.</string>
    <string name="descripcion2">Typically, the essential dish is the freshly caught trout in Las Trucheras, where the visitor can carry out his own fishery for this succulent fish, and have him prepared as he pleases. Additionally, the typical Antioquia cuisine, including the international Bandeja Paisa</string>
    <string name="descripcion3">In Jardín there are plans for all tastes, but one of the best ideas is to explore its paths in search of trekking routes and the imposing coffee landscape, you can also enjoy the adrenaline with the canopy (Zip Line). So if you want to explore all that Jardín has to offer, stay at least 3 days and fill up with energy to take advantage of this town.</string>
    <string name="descripcion4">In Jardín, Antioquia, you can find very colorful hostels and hotels and rural lodgings that preserve the local architecture and fuse it with artistic and sustainable proposals. We recommend you look at these accommodations that have biosecurity protocols: Charco Corazón Hostel, Valdivia Plaza Hotel, Plantación Hotel, Passiflora House, Kantarrana Urbana Hotel, Park Balconies and La Casona Hotel.</string>
    <string name="descripcion5">In Jardin we have some really wonderful landscapes such as the Cristo Rey viewpoint where you can appreciate a great panoramic view of Jardín and see all the mountains that surround it.When you decide to go down from the Cristo Rey Viewpoint, after going down you will have to do it along a very beautiful path that it goes through the pine forest, some banana groves, coffee plantations, and even a river. </string>


    <string name="Texto">My name is Enmanuel Vargas Jimenez, I am a labor technician student in software development at the CESDE education center.
    I am a freelance programmer, with enough dexterity to develop web pages and mobile apps, in addition to working in other fields within the concept of programming.</string>
    <string name="opcion1">About us</string>
    <string name="opcion2">English</string>
    <string name="opcion3">Spanish</string>


</resources>